Davis, Jackson; Papers apap141
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council, 1967-1997; 2; 2.50 cubic ft.
  - Town of Petersburg Planning Survey, 1989 (Box 4 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 10)
  - "Town of Sand Lake Master Plan", 1993 (Box 4 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 11)
  - "Comprehensive Plan: Town and Village of Nassau", circa 1970 (Oversized 1)
- Albany County Environmental Management Council and Four County Committee on Recycling, 1962, 1965-1966, 1968-1973, 3; 1 cubic ft.
  This series contains meeting minutes, reports, and subject files related to the Albany County Environmental Management Council and the related Four County Committee on Recycling (also called the Temporary Committee for Recycling for the Capital District Region.) The Council was formed in 1971 as an advisory body to the Albany County Commissioner of Health. Jackson Davis served as administrative assistant. The Four County Committee on Recycling, whose members represented the counties of Albany, Schenectady, Rennselaer, and Saratoga, was founded in 1972 to investigate the possibility of a recycling system proposal for the Capital District. The Council's primary focus was solid waste management and recycling. The series includes subject files with articles, publications, notes, and reports on these topics. There are also three research files on the environmental impact of oil refineries.
  - Albany County Environmental Advisory Council, Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 1)
  - Black Clawson Company, Franklin, Ohio Recycling Plant, Press Release and Promotional Photographs, 1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 2)
  - Binghamton Environmental Savings Targets, Report, 1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 3)
  - Community Clean-Up Campaign, Undated (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 4)
  - Environmental Quality Bond Act, 1973 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 5)
  - Four County Committee on Recycling, 1971-1973 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 6)
  - Four County Committee on Recycling, 1971-1973 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 7)
  - Keep New York State Clean Campaign, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 8)
  - Letter of Resignation, Jackson Davis, 1973 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 9)
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, Office of Recovery, Recycling, and Reuse, Progress Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 10)
  - New York State Environmental Plan, Pre-Hearing Draft, 1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 11)
  - Oil Refineries, Environmental Impact, General and Air Pollution, Articles, 1965; 1968-1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 12)
  - Oil Refineries, Environmental Impact, Notes, Undated (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 13)
  - Oil Refineries, Environmental Impact, Water, Noise, and Energy, 1968, 1970-1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 14)
  - Recycling, Articles, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 15)
  - Recycling, Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 16)
  - Recycling, G.E. Proposal, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 17)
  - Recycling, Legislative Acts, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 18)
  - Recycling, Memorandum, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 19)
  - Recycling, News Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 20)
  - Recycling, Notes, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 21)
  - Recycling, Pamphlets, Undated (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 22)
  - Recycling, Publications, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 23)
  - Recycling, Publications, 1972; Undated (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 24)
  - Recycling, Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 25)
  - Recycling Systems, 1970-1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 26)
  - Recycling Systems, Report, 1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 27)
  - "Refuse and Junk Disposal," Buck County Planning Commission, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 28)
  - "Report on Refuse Disposal," Onondaga County, 1967 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 29)
  - Solid Waste, Environmental Reporter, Current Developments, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 30)
  - Solid Waste Management, News Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Albany County Environmental Management Council and), Folder 31)
- Futures Group, 1966-1976; 4; 0.5 cubic ft.
  This series contains files related to Davis' involvement with the Futures Group of Glastonbury, Connecticut, founded in 1971. Much of the series relates to a Futures Group proposal to study public and private day care programs. The proposal and background research material are included. Also found in this series are four folders of bibliographic citations written on three by five cards. The significance of these citations is unclear.
  - Bibliographic Citations, 1972-1976 (Box 1 (4-Futures Group), Folder 1)
  - Bibliographic Citations, 1972-1976 (Box 1 (4-Futures Group), Folder 2)
  - Bibliographic Citations, 1972-1976 (Box 1 (4-Futures Group), Folder 3)
  - Bibliographic Citations, 1972-1976 (Box 1 (4-Futures Group), Folder 4)
  - Center for Coordination of Research on Social Indicators, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (4-Futures Group), Folder 5)
  - Day Care Centers and Productivity, Research, circa 1975 (Box 1 (4-Futures Group), Folder 6)
  - Day Care Project, Proposal, 1975 (Box 1 (4-Futures Group), Folder 7)
  - Day Care Project, Publications, 1966-1969 (Box 1 (4-Futures Group), Folder 8)
  - Day Care Project, Publications, 1971-1975 (Box 1 (4-Futures Group), Folder 9)
  - Department of Defense, "Value Engineering", 1968 (Box 1 (4-Futures Group), Folder 10)
  - Early Warning Signals Course and Second General Assembly, Registrant Lists, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Futures Group), Folder 1)
  - "Federal Support for Education Research and Related Activities," National Institute of Education, Preliminary Report, 1976 (Box 2 (4-Futures Group), Folder 2)
  - "Find Out About the Future: A Catalog of Resources," World Future Society, 1976 (Box 2 (4-Futures Group), Folder 3)
  - "The Futurescan System: An Approach to Environmental Monitoring, Forecasting, and Tracking," Lynne Cullum and Theodore Gordon, 1976 (Box 2 (4-Futures Group), Folder 4)
  - Land Use Forecasting, Reports, Notes, 1974-1976 (Box 2 (4-Futures Group), Folder 5)
  - "Science, Technology and World Problems," Theodore Gordon, Prepared for NASA, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Futures Group), Folder 6)
  - Technology Transfer Directory of People, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Futures Group), Folder 7)
- New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance, 1970-1972; 1973-1979; Undated; 5; 0.5 cubic ft.
  This series consists of subject files on a variety of topics related to food production and healthy diet. Topics include food suppliers, nutrition, natural foods, composting, food cooperatives, gardening, and insect control.
  - Articles, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 1)
  - Community Gardens, Newsletters, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 2)
  - Composting and Mulching, 1971; Undated (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 3)
  - Co-ops, 1977-1979 (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 4)
  - Co-ops, Undated (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 5)
  - Energy, 1979; Undated (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 6)
  - Farm Workers' Rights, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 7)
  - Farming, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 8)
  - Food and Energy, 1977; Undated (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 9)
  - Food and Nutrition, City of Syracuse Policy, 1976 (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 10)
  - Food Preservation, 1977 (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 11)
  - Food Prices, 1973 (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 12)
  - Food Suppliers, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 13)
  - Gardening, Undated (Box 1 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 14)
  - Greenhouses, 1974-1979; Undated (Box 2 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 1)
  - The Hunger Project, Newspaper, 1978 (Box 2 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 2)
  - Hydroponics, 1974; 1977 (Box 2 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 3)
  - Insect Control, 1970; 1975; 1978 (Box 2 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 4)
  - Leaflets, Fliers, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 5)
  - Natural Foods, 1975; 1977-1979; Undated (Box 2 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1979; Undated (Box 2 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 7)
  - Nutrition and Healthy Foods, 1975-1979; Undated (Box 2 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 8)
  - Self Reliance, Institute for Local Self Reliance, Newsletter, 1978 (Box 2 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 9)
  - Solar Energy, 1975; Undated (Box 2 (5-New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance), Folder 10)
  - Solar Survival, Solar Food Dehydrator, Plans, 1977 (Flat-file 1)
- Environmental Forum, 1967-1974; 6; 0.5 cubic ft.
  The series contains documents produced by the Environmental Forum class and public forum. These are primarily class handouts, class notes, and publications related to the class and the speakers who attended. In addition, there are materials related to the production of the first three issues of the "Environmental Issues" newsletter, produced for the Environment Studies program at the State University of New York at Albany.
  - Buloff, Jack, 1967-1970; 1973 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 1)
  - "Environmental Forum Bibliography and Index to Environmental Literature through 1970," Jack Bulloff, 1972 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 2)
  - Environmental Forum, Book Lists, 1969; Undated (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 3)
  - Environmental Forum, Exam, 1970 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 4)
  - Environmental Forum, Founding of Program, 1971-1971 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 5)
  - Environmental Forum, General, 1970 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 6)
  - Environmental Forum, Handouts and Notes, Spring Semester, 1970 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 7)
  - Environmental Forum, Miscellaneous Handouts and Notes, 1970-1974 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 8)
  - Environmental Forum, Summary Statements, Fall Semester, 1969 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 9)
  - Environmental Issues, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 10)
  - Environmental Issues, Editorials, 1971 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 11)
  - Environmental Issues, Issue 1, Drafts and Notes, 1971 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 12)
  - Environmental Issues, Issue 2, Drafts and Notes, 1971 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 13)
  - Environmental Issues, Issue 3, Drafts and Notes, 1971 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 14)
  - Environmental Issues, Issues 1-3, 1971 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 15)
  - Environmental Issues, Original Ideas, 1971 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 16)
  - Environmental Issues, Printing, 1971 (Box 1 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 17)
  - Environmental Problems, Citations of Books and Articles, Undated (Box 2 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 1)
  - Environmental Studies Course Descriptions, 1975; Undated (Box 2 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 2)
  - "Environmental Teach-In Booklist," Jackson Davis and Jack Bulloff, 1970 (Box 2 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 3)
  - Faculty Resources, 1967-1979; Undated (Box 2 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 4)
  - "Proposal for the Development of a Curriculum for Training Local Environmental Commission Members," Paul Marr, Grant Proposal, 1972 (Box 2 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 5)
  - Protect Your Environment Club, Information Committee, 1970 (Box 2 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 6)
  - Protect Your Environment Club, Introductory Remarks, 1970; Undated (Box 2 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 7)
  - Protect Your Environment Club, Minutes, Publications, Undated (Box 2 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 8)
  - "A Salient Bibliography of the Environment," Jack Bulloff and Jackson Davis, Undated (Box 2 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 9)
  - "The Uses of the Useless," Daniel McKinley, 1969 (Box 2 (6-Environmental Forum), Folder 10)
- Bibliographies, 1965-1985; Undated; 7; 0.66 cubic ft.
  This series contains bibliographies and bibliographic materials produced and collected by Jackson Davis in connection to the various environmental organizations he was a member of, particularly the Environmental Forum and the Futures Group. Much of the material consists of notes of citations and photocopies of indexes and other bibliographies. Several published bibliographies are included, some by Davis and some by Dr. Jack Bulloff, a professor at the State University of New York at Albany and contributor to the Environmental Forum. Notable is the "Documentalist in Environmental Studies" folder, which contains Davis' interpretation on the process of creating bibliographies. Bibliographies produced specifically for use in the Environmental Forum class are located in that series.
  - Air Pollution, Bibliography of Films, 1962-1969 (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 1)
  - Air Pollution, Bibliography, Notes, Undated (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 2)
  - Air Pollution, Course Materials, Grant Proposal, 1970 (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 3)
  - Air Pollution, Published Bibliographies, 1966-1970 (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 4)
  - Air Pollution Institute, 1970; Undated (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 5)
  - "An Air Pollution Study Guide for Junior High Schools and High School Science Teachers", Undated (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 6)
  - "Bibliography of Air Pollution Literature," Jackson Davis and Robert Nurnberger, Undated (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 7)
  - Book Bibliographies, 1965-1968 (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 8)
  - "Documentalist in Environmental Studies," Jackson D, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 9)
  - Environmental Bibliographies, Jack Bulloff, 1973 (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 10)
  - Environmental Index and Environmental Abstracts, 1973-1975 (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 11)
  - Environmental Problems, Miscellaneous Bibliographies, 1968; 1970-1975 (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 12)
  - "Firm Facts: Air Pollution, Bibliography of Congressional Material", Undated> (Box 1 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 13)
  - Indoor Air Pollution, 1973; 1982-1985 (Box 2 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 1)
  - Land Use Planning Abstracts, Undated (Box 2 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 2)
  - "Library of Congress Heading for Environmental Readings," Jack Bulloff and Jackson Davis, 1970 (Box 2 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 3)
  - "Open Lands Planning and Preservation, A Bibliography," Jackson Davis, 1972 (Box 2 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 4)
  - Pollution, Published Bibliographies, 1966-1967; 1971 (Box 2 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 5)
  - "A Selected Bibliography on a Multi-Disciplinary Approach to Environmental Impact Analysis", 1974 (Box 2 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 6)
  - Solar Energy Bibliography, Undated (Box 2 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 7)
  - Solar Energy Project, 1974-1975; Undated (Box 2 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 8)
  - "The Subject Bibliographer," Robert Burgess, Undated (Box 2 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 9)
  - "Thesaurus on Environmental Problems," Based on Questionnaire Replies to Protect Your Environment Club, 1970 (Box 2 (7-Bibliographies), Folder 10)
- Subject Files, 1956-1997; Undated; 8; 3.17 cubic ft.
  Included in this series are subject files of news clippings on various environmental topics. There are also files on numerous local environmental groups, many small and short lived. These folders often consist of only a single item, such as a leaflet or flier. Of interest are the "Job Applications" folder, which contains Jackson Davis' resumes and employment history. This represents almost all of the biographical material in this collection. Also of interest is the folder for the "Keep New York State Clean" program, for which Jackson Davis served as a coordinator.
  - Abortion, News Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - The Adirondack Council, Leaflet, 1985 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Adirondack Update, Newsletter, 1994 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, News Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Agriculture and Land Use Comic Books, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Air Pollution, News Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Alaska and the Arctic, News Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Albany Taxpayers Association, Newsletter, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - American Society of Planning Officials, Planner's Library, 1962-1973 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - American Society of Planning Officials, Planner's Library, 1962-1973 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Architecture, News Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Art, News Clippings, 1969 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Association for the Protection of Adirondack Park, Pamphlet, 1992 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - The Association of State Wetland Managers, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Audubon Society of the State on New York, Flier, Leaflets, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - AuSable Trails Institute for Environmental Studies, News Clipping, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Backyard Birds Nature Center, Newsletter, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Blue White Rainbow, Newsletter, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - "Business Guide for Reducing Solid Waste," EPA, 1993 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Bottle Bill, 1974 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - "A Buyers Guide to Environmental Media: Energy", circa 1973 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Capital District Solid Waste Environmental Education Program Committee (C.D. SWEEP), Minutes, Memorandum, 1973 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - C.T. Male Associates P.C., Leaflets, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - California, News Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Canal Recreationway Commission, Leaflet, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Capital Area Food Day, 1975 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Capital Area Recycling Effort, 1972; Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Capital District Cohousing Group, Poster, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Cartoons, Pictures, and Humor, News Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Center for the Environment and Man, 1969-1974 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Center for the Environment and Man, Inc., Corporate Profile, 1972 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Center for Environmental Information, Leaflet, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Center for Traditional Arts and Agriculture, Leaflet, 1993 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Chambers of Commerce, Contact Lists, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Chemical and Engineering News, Articles, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Chemicals, Chemical Warfare, and Biological Warfare, News Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Citizens' Environmental Coalition, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Citizens for a Better New York, 1972 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Colorado Plateau Environmental Advisory Council, Newsletter, 1970-1973 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Columbia County Hours, Leaflet, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Committee on Education in Environmental Conservation, Senate Bill, 1975 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Communications, News Clippings, 1969 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Community Referral Center, Reports, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Conferences, Lectures, and Speeches, News Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Congressional Record, 1975 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Connecticut Department of Environmental Protection Citizens' Bulletin, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Conservation, News Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Contact Lists, Albany Environmental Groups, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Contact Lists, Albany Environmental Groups, Index Cards, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Cornell Waste Management Institute, Leaflet, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1973; 1975 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, Answered, 1970 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, Dr. Louis Benezet, 1972 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Council of Community Services of the Albany Area, Publication Order Form, 1971 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Dams, News Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - "Defining the Quality of Life: Household Technology on Trial," Institute on Man and Science, 1972 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - "Delmar 1992, Technology Education," Publishing Catalog, Delmar Publishing, Inc. (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - "Directory of New York State Agencies Providing Services to Local Governments, 1971 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Earth Advocate Environmental Variety Store, Catalog, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Earth Day, Environmental Organizations Contact List, 1990 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Earth Day, Environmental Organizations Contact List, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Earth Day, Environmental Organizations Contact List, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Earth Day, Environmental Organizations Contact List, Undated (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Earth Day, News Clippings, 1970 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Earth Spirit Calls, Newsletter, 1993 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - Earth Week, State University of New York at Albany, 1973 (Box 1 (8-Subject Files), Folder 67)